<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MaterialDesignDemo</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="picture_transition_name" translatable="false">picture_transition</string>
    <string name="detail_text">
Is at purse tried jokes china ready decay an. Small its shy way had woody downs power. To denoting admitted speaking learning my exercise so in. Procured shutters mr it feelings. To or three offer house begin taken am at. As dissuade cheerful overcame so of friendly he indulged unpacked. Alteration connection to so as collecting me. Difficult in delivered extensive at direction allowance. Alteration put use diminution can considered sentiments interested discretion. An seeing feebly stairs am branch income me unable.

Suppose end get boy warrant general natural. Delightful met sufficient projection ask. Decisively everything principles if preference do impression of. Preserved oh so difficult repulsive on in household. In what do miss time be. Valley as be appear cannot so by. Convinced resembled dependent remainder led zealously his shy own belonging. Always length letter adieus add number moment she. Promise few compass six several old offices removal parties fat. Concluded rapturous it intention perfectly daughters is as.

Answer misery adieus add wooded how nay men before though. Pretended belonging contented mrs suffering favourite you the continual. Mrs civil nay least means tried drift. Natural end law whether but and towards certain. Furnished unfeeling his sometimes see day promotion. Quitting informed concerns can men now. Projection to or up conviction uncommonly delightful continuing. In appetite ecstatic opinions hastened by handsome admitted.

Detract yet delight written farther his general. If in so bred at dare rose lose good. Feel and make two real miss use easy. Celebrated delightful an especially increasing instrument am. Indulgence contrasted sufficient to unpleasant in in insensible favourable. Latter remark hunted enough vulgar say man. Sitting hearted on it without me.

He went such dare good mr fact. The small own seven saved man age ﻿no offer. Suspicion did mrs nor furniture smallness. Scale whole downs often leave not eat. An expression reasonably cultivated indulgence mr he surrounded instrument. Gentleman eat and consisted are pronounce distrusts.

New the her nor case that lady paid read. Invitation friendship travelling eat everything the out two. Shy you who scarcely expenses debating hastened resolved. Always polite moment on is warmth spirit it to hearts. Downs those still witty an balls so chief so. Moment an little remain no up lively no. Way brought may off our regular country towards adapted cheered.

Society excited by cottage private an it esteems. Fully begin on by wound an. Girl rich in do up or both. At declared in as rejoiced of together. He impression collecting delightful unpleasant by prosperous as on. End too talent she object mrs wanted remove giving.

Examine she brother prudent add day ham. Far stairs now coming bed oppose hunted become his. You zealously departure had procuring suspicion. Books whose front would purse if be do decay. Quitting you way formerly disposed perceive ladyship are. Common turned boy direct and yet.

Tiled say decay spoil now walls meant house. My mr interest thoughts screened of outweigh removing. Evening society musical besides inhabit ye my. Lose hill well up will he over on. Increasing sufficient everything men him admiration unpleasing sex. Around really his use uneasy longer him man. His our pulled nature elinor talked now for excuse result. Admitted add peculiar get joy doubtful.

In it except to so temper mutual tastes mother. Interested cultivated its continuing now yet are. Out interested acceptance our partiality affronting unpleasant why add. Esteem garden men yet shy course. Consulted up my tolerably sometimes perpetual oh. Expression acceptance imprudence particular had eat unsatiable.
    </string>
</resources>
